Good day, my friends. This is con
and I'm your financial advisor. Do you want to
have a 100,000 inheritance for
your children, the kind that you don't have
on earth anymore? You still have
support given to them. Well, that
's possible with Sunlight Sun Smarter
Life Elite Peso 10. That's possible because
the company guarantees 8% of the face
amount approved to us. So how is that?
This is a life insurance for 5 or 10
years. So we have two options to
choose from. How long will we
save? We will have a
guaranteed payout. Yes, which is the 88%,
so to get that 100,000. We will be
needing
1.25 million face amount. Or is that
called an
endowment plan? So if
our face amount is 1.25 million, then it's
going to be
100,000. That's in addition to the Deb benefit.
We can get it because the Deb
benefit is the 1.25 million tendency.
We have a living benefit. It always
starts.  after you pay the
6th Year of your policy So imagine if
the term you chose is 10 years you
will save
you have not finished saving for 10
years in the sixth year you have
one
Php1,000 and take note This is not a one
time you can get this once every other
year until age 100 yes
100 so what if at 101 it is not
matured is that another feature
it once You have finished the 10 years
or the 5 years If that is what you chose you will not
lose the insurance
coverage which is the 1.25 million there is no more
extra charges
charges so you do not have to die
early just to benefit from the
benefits of what you saved I'm sorry
So another thing
this plan is multipurpose because the cash you get
give me the money you can
use it for an educational fund and
when you finish what
you studied you can
use it for a retirement fund or
other life milestones like a travel
fund because it is cash cash  That's 100,000
okay another recession proof this is
why the amount doesn't change
it doesn't depend on the stock
market it doesn't have that anymore
the company guarantees
how much we can get so
we can immediately project how
much should I save to
guarantee I have this amount
in this particular period okay hence if
you find this policy very interesting
and you think it's perfect for your
needs ' ba that You have
passive income just letting your money
work for you Plus we still have insurance
and you want to start Ong this policy now
Don't forget to book a free discovery
call so I can do a sample
computation based on your age and your
status Okay ya